## ain Meulders

35, rue du Pélican, 1000 Brussels, Belgium

□ (+32) 0498.526.425 | ■ meulders.a@qmail.com | ★ jocko.consulting | meuldersa | Driving Licence



## **Summary**

With 8+ years of experience, specializing in web development, using the technology and SEO to drive traffic and enguage users, I've developed, build, deployed and maintain different web sites, intranet and tools, working on new and existing products, following architectural rules. Nerd enjoying to customize all of the terminal/desktop environment and keep learning new technologies and tools.

## Work Experience \_\_\_\_

**GSK** Wavre, Belgium

SENIOR .NET DEVELOPER

Sep. 2016 - Feb. 2017

- · Implemented a COM add-in EXCEL. Laboratory's data for the indirect tests are encoded in an Excel file. These data must be adapted and available in an Excel Sheet in order to meet statistical service's requirements.
- Implemented an COM add-in EXCEL in .NET allowing secure and centralized module integration in all GSK Excel's projects.
- RSV Sytem: Excel VBA system with secure authentification and centralized audit allowing raw data import from Quant Studio software, data reduction, reporting and analyse on the calculated data, results can be injected both in Cristal and QC Chart softwares.

**DECATHLON** Lille, France

SENIOR .NET DEVELOPER

Mar. 2016 - Jul. 2016

· Developed an easy-to-use gift card module which integrate the selling process and replace the hard to use tools in the ERP (WAZABEE). The module allow payment on the web site, gift cards selling and customisation in ERP and web.

**AG INSURANCE** Brussels, Belgium

SENIOR .NET DEVELOPER

Mar. 2014 - Sep. 2015

- As a lead developer, involved in the full rewrite of the NewClaims project in HTML5 and responsive design.
- As a lead developer, build a site for the affiliates allowing them to access their declarations in one clic. secure EID module, WCF interfaces, COBOL transactions.
- Winform app allowing to analyse the mainframe transaction messages.
- Manage **Biztalk**'s "case clients". (documents indexation)
- Display an affiliate health contract's overview based on search criteria. Portal access.
- Provide online access to "AG Benefits" contracts. (migration)

### **TAGORA / JWT Brussels** Brussels, Belgium

JUNIOR / MEDIOR .NET DEVELOPER

Mar. 2008 - Nov. 2013

- Development for Dieteren (Audi, Skoda, Seat, Volswagen): CMS based plateforms Umbraco, prospects tools, contests web sites and tablet apps. Different admin tools (prospect list management, **Selligent** campaign, **Analytics** dashboards).
- Implemented different contests web sites (BEOBANK, VOO, COCA-COLA, CARLSBERG)
- Degroof Bank: CMS (Sharepoint 2007) based plateforms (custom templates, jobs and library). Module for SICAV integration in the CMS, dynamic generation of PDF based on XML data uploaded mensually by the Bank. Videos module.
- AWEX: CMS (Sharepoint 2007) based plateforms (custom templates, jobs and library). Inscription module.
- Tom and Co: Web site development to promote weekly products. Custom backend for product management. Different modules (mail box, pet loss, pet finder, games ...)

### Certifications

2019	Google Digital Labs Certificate, Digital Marketing	Belgium
2015	People Centric Certified, .NET Class A Certificate	Belgium
2012	Microsoft Certified Professional. Certification Number: E906-4019	Belaium

ALAIN MEULDERS · CURICULUM VITAE

# Alain Meulders

### FULL STACK .NET DEVELOPER

35, rue du Pélican, 1000, Brussels, Belgium

□ (+32) 0498.526.425 | ■ meulders.a@gmail.com | 🏕 jocko.consulting | 🛅 meuldersa | Driving Licence

### Technical Skills

**OS** Windows, Linux

**DevOps** AWS, Azure, Docker, Kubernetes, JenkinsX

**Database** SQL Server, Sybase, REDIS

**Back-end** ASP.NET, REST API, WCF, Umbraco

**Front-end** Bootstrap, Hugo, Redux, React, HTML5, SASS, Javascript

**Programming** C#, Python, Bash

**Tools** Visual Studio, SQL Management Studio, TFS

**Architecture and Methodologies** Agile, Design patterns

**Others** JIRA, GIT, Google Analytics, Documentation

### Softs Skills\_

Capacity to work alone following priorities

Capacity to work in a structured way following the procedures

Capacity to follow the architecture rules and norms

Capacity to communicate realistic development prevision

### **Education**

### **LUMINY (Aix-Marseille Faculty of Sciences)**

Marseille, France

1999

BACHELOR DEGREE IN MATHEMATICS AND COMPUTER SCIENCE

- French: Mother tongue
- English: Full professional capacity (1 year in London/City&Guilds 3792-986 Literacy Level2 2007)